Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. New business records, 1924-2007 and undated, bulk 1980-1989 RL.00731
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Companies Files, 1946-2005 and undated, 72 boxes
  - Unilever
    - Lever Brothers, 1953 Nov.-1963 (Milton Moskowitz files) (Box 85)
    - Trends in Total Advertising Expenditure in 25 Countries, 1970-1979, 1980 (Box 85)
  - United Dairy Industry Association/National Dairy Promotion and Research Board (UDIA/NDB)
    - General files, 1993 (Box 85)
    - Agency review, 1993 (Box 85)
    - Shopping List agency pamphlet, 1993 (Box 85)
  - United States Marine Corps (USMC)
    - Answers to U.S. Marine Corps Advertising Questionnaire, 1963 May 21 (Box 85)
    - Resolicitation material, 1982 (Box 85)
  - United States Navy
    - General files, 1987 (Box 85)
    - Advertising plan, 1986-1987 (Box 85)
    - Agency presentation, circa 1986 (Box 85)
    - Bob Pitman interview on market, 1987 (Box 85)
    - Military print advertising, 1986-1987 (Box 85)
    - Navy Blue campaign, 1987 June (Box 85)
    - Navy recruiting advertising services, 1987 (Box 85)
    - Overview, 1986 (Box 86)
    - Technical proposal, 1987, 3 folders (Box 86)
  - United States Postal Service (USPS)
    - Competition and Change presentation, 1983 (Box 86)
    - JWT presentation to U.S.P.S., 1983 (Box 86)
    - Annual reports, 1987-1988 (Box 86)
  - U.S. Brewers Association
    - General files, 1962 July (Milton Moskowitz files) (Box 86)
  - U.S. Lines
    - General files, 1957 July-1962 Feb. (Milton Moskowitz files) (Box 86)
  - Visa
    - General files, 1987 and undated (Box 86)
    - Credit Card Industry: Poised for Change, 1986 (Box 86)
  - Von's
    - [JWT-USA--Von's and the More Agency, 1987: Moved to Oversize Materials], 7 folders (Box 86)
    - Supermarket industry presentation, 1986-1987 (Box 86)
    - Von's and West Coast supermarkets general file, 1987 (Box 87)
  - Wall Street Journal
    - Background packet, 1989, 2 folders (Box 87)
  - Walt Disney Productions
    - General files, 1964 Nov. (Milton Moskowitz files) (Box 87)
  - Walt Disney World
    - Proposal for a Strategic Partnership, 1994, 2 folders (Box 87)
  - Warner-Lambert
    - General files, 1954 Nov.-1964 Feb. (Milton Moskowitz files) (Box 87)
    - American Chicle Company, 1954 Sep.-1962 July (Milton Moskowitz files) (Box 87)
    - Emerson Drug Company, Bromo Seltzer, 1949 Dec.-1960 Feb. (Milton Moskowitz files) (Box 87)
  - W.F. Young
    - General files, 1959 July-1965 Aug. (Milton Moskowitz files) (Box 87)
  - The Wine Advisory Board
    - General files, 1955 July-1961 June (Milton Moskowitz files) (Box 87)
  - Zale Corporation
    - General files, 1986-1987 (Box 87)
    - Agency review and selection, 1987 (Box 87)
    - Annual report, 1986 (Box 87)
    - Jewelry questionnaire, undated (Box 87)
    - JWT mission, circa 1986 (Box 87)
    - [JWT-USA-- Zale Corporation, DeBeers proof, 1986: Moved to Oversize Materials] (Box 87)
    - Refashioning of Zales (Modern Jeweler article), 1986 (Box 87)
- Product Category Files, 1975-1992 and undated, 3 boxes
  - Airlines
    - Category spending, 1992, 2 folders (Box 88)
    - International airlines, clippings, 1986 (Box 88)
  - Banks
    - Citibank, 1991 (Box 88)
    - Society: Banking with Human Interest presentation, undated (Box 88)
    - Voice of Manufacturers Hanover, communications audit proposal, undated (Box 88)
  - Cigarettes
    - General files, 1975 (Box 88)
      [Includes trademark research, presentation draft for Salem cigarettes]
    - Clippings, 1986 (Box 88)
  - Cosmetics & Fragrances
    - Avon & Cosmetic Industry--Brief Overview, 1989 (Box 88)
    - Fragrance, Makeup & Skin--Core Reviews--Vol. II--Makeup Industry, 1985 (Box 88)
    - Review of US skin care industry, undated (Box 88)
    - Revlon background, 1986 (Box 88)
  - Cruise Lines
    - General files, 1981-1985 (Box 88)
    - Clippings, 1982-1985 (Box 88)
  - Feminine hygiene
    - Explanation of Consumer Image in Tampon Market, 1983 (Box 88)
    - Feminine Care Market Situation Analysis, 1983 (Box 88)
    - Feminine care products, 1982 (Box 88)
    - Johnson & Johnson, 1981 (Box 88)
    - New business prospects, 1984 (Box 88)
    - Playtex, review of tampon category, 1992 (Box 88)
    - Tambrand news stories, 1990-1991 (Box 89)
    - U.S. Consumer Media: A Brief Review of Expenditures, Dimensions, Trends, & Characteristics, 1993 (Box 89)
  - Food
    - Baked goods
      - clippings, 1980-1985 (Box 89)
      - Tear sheets, 1982-1986 (Box 89)
      - Wonder Bread: An Idea for the Future, circa 1987 (Box 89)
    - Creative department file, 1985 (Box 89)
    - Facts of Life: The Changing Supermarket Shopper, 1985 (Box 89)
    - Fast food industry prospects, 1988 (Box 89)
    - Frozen Foods
      - Defrosting Lean Cuisine: JWT Explores the Frozen Food Market, 1984 (Box 89)
      - Frozen food entree situation analysis, 1986 (Box 89)
      - Mrs. Paul's, 1986 (Box 89)
      - U.S. frozen foods market, circa 1978 (Box 89)
    - Pasta, rice, and grains, 1985-1986
      - Competitive overview--pasta dinner mixes, 1986 (Box 89)
      - Pasta toss competitive review, 1985 (Box 89)
      - Prepared rice competitive review, 1986 (Box 89)
      - Project Clover competitive positioning report, 1986 (Box 89)
      - Project Clover competitive review, 1986 (Box 89)
      - Rice industry, 1958 Apr.-Oct. (Milton Moskowitz files) (Box 90)
      - Spaghetti sauces competitive review (for R.J. French), 1986 (Box 90)
      - Spice Your Rice: Competitive Review and Advertising Test Recommendations, 1985 (Box 90)
    - Restaurant industry prospects, 1988 (Box 90)
    - Trends in U.S. food consumption, circa 1987 (Box 90)
  - Furniture
    - Market projections, undated (Box 90)
  - Healthcare
    - General files, 1986-1987 (Box 90)
    - Over-the-counter medications, 1988 and undated (Box 90)
  - Jeans
    - General files, 1979-1985 (Box 90)
    - U.S. Jeans Market, 1981, 2 folders (Box 90)
    - V.F. Corporation annual report, 1983 (Box 90)
    - Wrangler, 1984-1985 (Box 90)
  - Light bulbs
    - Consumer interviews, 1986 (Box 90)
  - Mutual funds
    - General files, 1987 (Box 90)
    - Clippings, 1985-1986 (Box 90)
  - Real Estate
    - General files, 1988-1989 (Box 90)
- Chicago Office Additions, 1973-2007 and undated; 1
  - General Files, 1983-2007 and undated; 1
    - Account gains/losses, 1983-1995 (Box CH1)
    - Case studies, undated (Box CH1)
    - Credentials presentations, 1990-2001; 8 folders (Box CH1)
    - Credentials presentation, 2004 (Box CH2)
    - Credentials submission, 2007 (Box CH2)
    - Engine Room legal, trademark application, 1994-1996 (Box CH68)
    - Example from Hal Riney (Kinko's), undated (Box CH2)
    - JWT Media Department, undated (Box CH2)
    - New Business Checklist for Winners, 1992 (Box CH2)
    - New business mailings, 1991; 2 folders (Box CH2)
    - New business mailing "Baseballs", 1992; 2 folders (Box CH2)
    - New business mailing "Effies", 1990 (Box CH2)
    - New business mailing "Listener", 1993 (Box CH3)
    - New business mailing "Lunchables", 1990; 2 folders (Box CH3)
    - New business mailing "Write if you want work", 1990 (Box CH3)
    - New business mailing "Zagat Guide", 1990-1993; 2 folders (Box CH3)
    - New business prospect sheets, 2002 (Box CH3)
    - New credentials, 2001 (Box CH68)
    - Past questionnaires binders A-D, 1995-1998 (Box CH3)
    - Past questionnaires binders A-N, 1995-1998; 7 folders (Box CH4)
    - Past questionnaires binders O-Z, 1995-1998; 4 folders (Box CH5)
    - Pea Pods information, 1996; 4 folders (Box CH5)
    - Pea Pod digital items, undated (Box CH5)
  - New Business Prospects, 1973-2007 and undated; 2
    - Abbott Laboratories, 2006 (Box CH6)
    - Adolph Coors, 1983-1984 (Box CH6)
    - Adolph Coors--Communications/reactions test, 1978 (Box CH6)
    - Adolph Coors--Corporate communications recommendations, 1978 (Box CH6)
    - Adolph Coors--Herman Joseph, 1983; 2 folders (Box CH6)
    - Adolph Coors--Herman Joseph presentation, undated; 2 folders (Box CH6)
    - Adolph Coors--JWT profile, 1983 (Box CH6)
    - Adolph Coors--JWT profile, 1984 (Box CH7)
    - Adolph Coors--New business torch strategy, 1996 (Box CH7)
    - Adolph Coors--Survey of internal communications, 1978 (Box CH7)
    - Amazon, 2000 (Box CH7)
    - American Automobile Association (AAA), 2005 (Box CH7)
    - American Egg Board, 1992-1993; 2 folders (Box CH7)
    - American Society of Plastic and Reconstructive Surgeons (ASPRS), 1999; 2 folders (Box CH7)
    - American Soybean Association, 1990 (Box CH7)
    - Amtrak, 1995; 4 folders (Box CH7)
    - Amtrak, 1995 (Box CH8)
    - Anheuser-Busch, 1978 (Box CH8)
    - AON Group, 1997-1998; 5 folders (Box CH8)
    - AON Group--Creative review, 1997 (Box CH8)
    - AON--Print ads, undated (Box CH69)
    - Applebee's, 2007; 2 folders (Box CH8)
    - Archipelago, 2000 (Box CH9)
    - ATA Airlines, 2000-2001; 2 folders (Box CH9)
    - ATA Airlines--Charting a new destination, 2001 (Box CH9)
    - ATA Airlines--Key summary update on airline industry, 2000 (Box CH9)
    - ATA Airlines--Project Peanut, 2000 (Box CH9)
    - Barney (See also Lyons Group), 1994-1995 (Box CH9)
    - Barney--Correspondence, 1994-1995 (Box CH9)
    - Barney--Key learnings from 1995, 1996 (Box CH10)
    - Barney--What's inside the Barney Bag?, 1994 (Box CH10)
    - Beatrice Foods, 1977-1983; 4 folders (Box CH10)
    - Beatrice Foods--Charmglow, 1975-1976 (Box CH10)
    - Beatrice Foods--JWT credentials book, undated (Box CH10)
    - Beatrice Foods--JWT profile, 1983 (Box CH10)
    - Beatrice Foods--Meeting binder, 1983; 3 folders (Box CH11)
    - Beatrice Foods--Project Hazel, 1983; 2 folders (Box CH11)
    - Beatrice Foods--Response to questionnaire, 1983 (Box CH11)
    - Bellsouth--"Who's at BellSouth", 1998 (Box CH11)
    - Beltone Electronics, 1993-1999 (Box CH11)
    - Beltone Electronics--Presentations, undated (Box CH12)
    - Best Buy, 1995 (Box CH12)
    - Binny and Smith, 1997-2000 (Box CH12)
    - Black and Decker--Correspondence, 1991-1993 (Box CH12)
    - Blockbuster, 1998 (Box CH12)
    - Blockbuster--Video games, 1998 (Box CH12)
    - Blue Cross, 1992-1999; 2 folders (Box CH12)
    - Blue Cross--Booklet, 2001 (Box CH12)
    - Boeing, 2001 (Box CH12)
    - Boeing, 2001 (Box CH69)
    - Boeing--6 subsidiaries, 2000 (Box CH68)
    - Boeing--Outlook on business travel, 2000 (Box CH12)
    - Boeing--Company information, 2001 (Box CH12)
    - Boeing--Domestic travel market report, 2000 (Box CH12)
    - Boeing--Executive biographies, 2001 (Box CH12)
    - Boeing--Project Frontier, 1999-2001 (Box CH12)
    - Boeing--Project Frontier, 1999-2001; 4 folders (Box CH13)
    - Boeing--Road warriors: Business leaders cope with living away from home, 2000 (Box CH13)
    - Boise Cascade, 1995 (Box CH13)
    - Bombardier, 1995-1996; 3 folders (Box CH13)
    - Bombardier, 1996 (Box CH69)
    - Bombardier--Pitch materials, 1996 (Box CH13)
    - Bombardier--Presentations, 1996; 8 folders (Box CH13)
    - Bombardier--Presentations, 1996 and undated; 3 folders (Box CH14)
    - Bombardier--Sales pitch, 1996 (Box CH14)
    - Bonanza Restaurants, 1994; 2 folders (Box CH14)
    - Bonanza Restaurants--Correspondence, 1994 (Box CH14)
    - Bonanza Restaurants--Presentation, 1994 (Box CH14)
    - Boots the Chemist (Now Boots UK), 1995 (Box CH14)
    - Boots the Chemist--Boots visit, 1995-1996 (Box CH14)
    - Boots the Chemist--Presentation "A snapshot of Britain", 1995 (Box CH14)
    - Boston Consulting Group, 2000 (Box CH14)
    - Boston Consulting Group--Journal "Notes from our journey", 2000 (Box CH14)
    - Boston Consulting Group--Presentation "135 years of communication leadership", undated (Box CH14)
    - Bradford Exchange, 1999-2000 (Box CH15)
    - Braniff International, 1981 (Box CH15)
    - Branson--Charley Pride Theatre, 1994 (Box CH15)
    - Branson--Correspondence, 1994 (Box CH15)
    - Branson--Final presentation, 1994 (Box CH15)
    - Britannica.com, 1999 (Box CH15)
    - Britannica.com--Ads, 1999 (Box CH15)
    - Britannica.com--Presentations, 1999 (Box CH15)
    - British Airways--Correspondence, 1993-1995 (Box CH15)
    - British Airways--Correspondence, 1993 (Box CH68)
    - Budget Rent-A-Car, 1982-1996; 3 folders (Box CH15)
    - Budget Rent-A-Car--Focus groups, corporate history, 1995 (Box CH15)
    - Budget Rent-A-Car--Master file presentations, 1996 (Box CH15)
    - Budget Rent-A-Car--Positioning, 1995 (Box CH15)
    - Budget Rent-A-Car--Presentation "Auto rental industry overview", 1996 (Box CH15)
    - Burger King--Correspondence, 1991-1994 (Box CH15)
    - Burger King--Presentation "Back to the basics", 1993 (Box CH15)
    - Cadbury Schweppes, 1998 (Box CH16)
    - California Lottery--Mailing, 1992 (Box CH16)
    - Canon USA Inc., undated (Box CH16)
    - CareerBuilder--Request for proposal, 2002 (Box CH16)
    - Carnival Cruise Lines, 2001 (Box CH16)
    - Carpet and Rug Institute--Booklet "Answers to your questions", 1997 (Box CH16)
    - Carpet and Rug Institute--Correspondence, 1997 (Box CH16)
    - Carpet and Rug Institute--Drawings, undated (Box CH69)
    - Carpet and Rug Institute--General agency data, 1997 (Box CH16)
    - Carpet and Rug Institute--JWT book, 1997 (Box CH16)
    - Carpet and Rug Institute--Questionnaire, 1997 (Box CH16)
    - Carpet and Rug Institute--Rug sample, undated (Box CH16)
    - Career Builder--Newspaper, 2002 (Box CH69)
    - Cars.com, 2001; 2 folders (Box CH16)
    - Cars.com--Customer research final presentation, 1997 (Box CH17)
    - Cars.com--Gomez online consumer survey, 2000; 2 folders (Box CH17)
    - Cars.com--Gomez report "The state of online auto buying", 2001 (Box CH17)
    - Cars.com--New Autoshopper.com study executive summary, 2000 (Box CH17)
    - Cars.com--Photos, undated (Box CH17)
    - Cars.com--Pitch research materials, 2001 (Box CH17)
    - Cars.com--Presentations, 1999-2001; 6 folders (Box CH17)
    - Cars.com--Storyboards, 2001 (Box CH17)
    - Cars.com--Used Authoshopper.com study executive summary, 2000 (Box CH17)
    - Carson Pirie Scott and Co.--Annual report, 1994 (Box CH17)
    - Caterpillar--Wolverine footwear, 1997 (Box CH17)
    - Cellular One, 1995 (Box CH17)
    - Cellular One--Company booklet "Listen, share, and deliver", 2002 (Box CH17)
    - Cellular One--JWT background, 1995 (Box CH17)
    - Cellular One--Meetings and Effie Awards, 1994-1995 (Box CH18)
    - Cellular One--Presentation "Spot buying", undated (Box CH18)
    - Chicago Bears, 2007 (Box CH18)
    - Chicago History Museum, 2006 (Box CH18)
    - Chicago Mercantile Exchange, 1999 and undated; 2 folders (Box CH18)
    - Chicago Mercantile Exchange--An introduction to futures and options, 1996 (Box CH18)
    - Chicago Mercantile Exchange--Annual report, 1998 (Box CH18)
    - Chicago Mercantile Exchange--Brochures, 1995-1999 (Box CH18)
    - Chicago Mercantile Exchange--Brochure "The Merc at work", 1994, 1999 (Box CH68)
    - Chicago Mercantile Exchange--Presentation, 1999 (Box CH18)
    - Chicago White Sox, 1998; 2 folders (Box CH18)
    - Chiquita Brands, 1998 (Box CH18)
    - Chiquita Brands--Booklets, 1998; 2 folders (Box CH18)
    - Chuck-E-Cheese--Correspondence with buying guidelines, presentations, 1993 (Box CH19)
    - Chuck-E-Cheese--Presentation, 1993 (Box CH19)
    - Chuck-E-Cheese--Presentations: First 100 days; Showbiz Pizza Time Inc., 1993 (Box CH19)
    - Citibank--Citibank global branding, 1995 (Box CH19)
    - Citibank--Correspondence, 1995 (Box CH19)
    - Citibank--Global branding assignment, 1997 (Box CH19)
    - Citibank--Pitch in France, 1996 (Box CH19)
    - Citibank--Power of a brand, 1996 (Box CH19)
    - Citibank--Presentation "What we are learning", 1996 (Box CH19)
    - Claire's Boutiques, 1992 (Box CH19)
    - Clorox, 1995-1996; 2 folders (Box CH19)
    - Clorox--Correspondence, 1996 (Box CH68)
    - CNA Financial--Correspondence, 1995 (Box CH19)
    - Coca-Cola--"Who's who at Coca-Cola", 1998 (Box CH19)
    - Cole Haan--Correspondence, 1992-1993 (Box CH19)
    - Coleman--Coleman for Kids, 1994-1999 (Box CH19)
    - Coleman--Correspondence, 1993-1994 (Box CH19)
    - Coleman--Presentations, 1993 and undated; 2 folders (Box CH19)
    - Compaq--Annual report, 1994 (Box CH20)
    - Compaq-Correspondence, 1991-1994 (Box CH20)
    - Compaq--Digital new business pitch, 1993 (Box CH20)
    - Continental Airlines, 1997 (Box CH20)
    - Continental Airlines--Presentation, 1997 (Box CH20)
    - Control Data Institute, 1981-1984; 4 folders (Box CH20)
    - Control Data Institute--External correspondence, 1982-1984 (Box CH20)
    - Cub Foods--Client list, presentation preparation, 1994 (Box CH20)
    - Cub Foods--Lifestages of the American Consumer, 1995 (Box CH69)
    - Cub Foods--Presentation "Grocery shopping food for thought", 1994 (Box CH20)
    - Day runners--Background research, 1996 (Box CH21)
    - Dell, 1997 (Box CH21)
    - Dell--Briefing "Key issues as they see them", 1997 (Box CH21)
    - Dell--Presentation "Branding discussion", 1997 (Box CH21)
    - Dell--Presentation "Global credentials and due diligence", 1997 (Box CH21)
    - Dell--Presentation "Helping to build the brand', 1997 (Box CH21)
    - Dell--Presentation "Leveraging brand power", 1997 (Box CH21)
    - Dell--Request for information, 1997 (Box CH21)
    - DMI--Presentation "The JWT advantage", 1995 (Box CH21)
    - Evans Inc., 1982 (Box CH21)
    - Famous Footwear, 1993 (Box CH21)
    - FedEx--Background research, 1992 (Box CH21)
    - Fisher-Price, 1993 (Box CH21)
    - First Union, 1995 (Box CH21)
    - Florida USA--Contract, 1998 (Box CH21)
    - Florida USA--Florida visitor survey, 2000 (Box CH21)
    - Florida USA--Insertion schedule, 2000 (Box CH68)
    - Florida USA--JWT booklet, 2001 (Box CH21)
    - Florida USA--Pre-bid conference, small partner co-op ad menu, 2001-2002 (Box CH22)
    - Florida USA--Request for proposal, 1998 (Box CH22)
    - Florsheim, 1990-1994; 4 folders (Box CH22)
    - Florsheim--Correspondence and briefing, 1992-1994 (Box CH68)
    - Formica, 1996 (Box CH22)
    - Fox--Project X, 1996; 2 folders (Box CH22)
    - Freedrive.com, 2000; 3 folders (Box CH22)
    - Frigidaire--Presentation, 1994 (Box CH23)
    - Frito-Lay, 1997 (Box CH23)
    - FTD, 1999 (Box CH23)
    - FTD--Presentations, 1994-1995 (Box CH23)
    - FTD--Presentation, undated (Box CH69)
    - Gateway, 1996-1997; 2 folders (Box CH23)
    - Gateway--"Moms: The assignment" and creative brief, 1997 (Box CH23)
    - Gateway--Presentations, 1996-1997 and undated; 5 folders (Box CH23)
    - Gateway--Project Dakota, 1996 (Box CH23)
    - Gateway--Strategy presentation, 1996-1997 (Box CH23)
    - General Electric, 1997 (Box CH24)
    - Gerber Products, 1991-1996; 4 folders (Box CH24)
    - Gerber Products--Articles, 1994-1996 (Box CH69)
    - Giant Eagle--The fact sheet, 1998 (Box CH24)
    - Gillette, 2000-2001 (Box CH24)
    - Gillette, 1998 (Box CH68)
    - Glidden, 1993-1995 (Box CH24)
    - Glidden--Correspondence, 1993-1995 (Box CH68)
    - Golden Grain--Correspondence, 1994 (Box CH24)
    - Goody's Family Clothing, 1994; 2 folders (Box CH24)
    - Goody's Family Clothing--Presentations, 1994 (Box CH25)
    - Grand Met, 1996 (Box CH25)
    - H&R Block, 1980 (Box CH25)
    - H&R Block--Consumer attitude study, 1980 (Box CH25)
    - H&R Block--Local Broadcast buying, 1980 (Box CH25)
    - H&R Block--Potential growth, 1980 (Box CH25)
    - H&R Block--Qualitative exploration of consumer attitudes, 1980 (Box CH25)
    - H&R Block--Research synthesis, 1979 (Box CH25)
    - H&R Block--Study of tax preparation, 1980 (Box CH25)
    - H&R Block--T-Plan, 1980 (Box CH25)
    - Hallmark Cards, 1981 (Box CH25)
    - Health-O-Meter, 1992 (Box CH25)
    - Heineken, 1992-1998; 2 folders (Box CH25)
    - Heinz, 1998-1999 (Box CH25)
    - Heinz--Presentation "Victory for Heinz", 1999 (Box CH25)
    - Helene Curtis/Skin Care, 1996 (Box CH26)
    - Helene Curtis/Skin Care--Presentation "The impact of the Helene Curtis acquisition on Unilever's worldwide hair care portfolio strategy", 1996 (Box CH26)
    - Helene Curtis/Skin care--Request for proposal, 1998 (Box CH26)
    - Hertz, 1994 (Box CH26)
    - Hewlett-Packard, 1996 (Box CH26)
    - Hewlett-Packard--JWT booklet, 1996 and undated; 2 folders (Box CH26)
    - Hill's Department Stores, 1996 (Box CH26)
    - Hilton--Correspondence, 1997 (Box CH26)
    - Holiday Inn--Correspondence, 1992-1004 (Box CH27)
    - Holiday Inn--Correspondence, 1993-1994 (Box CH68)
    - Holland America Lines--Correspondence, travel agent magazines, 2001 (Box CH27)
    - Homeowners Loan Corporation--Request for proposal, 2002 (Box CH27)
    - Honeywell, 1995; 2 folders (Box CH27)
    - Honeywell, 1995 (Box CH69)
    - Hoover, 1991-1999 (Box CH27)
    - Hoover--JWT booklet, undated (Box CH27)
    - Hoover--Presentations, 1992 (Box CH27)
    - Hoover--Project Wind Tunnel, 1999 (Box CH27)
    - Household International, 1995-2001 (Box CH27)
    - Household International, 1995-2001 and undated; 3 folders (Box CH28)
    - Hyatt Hotels, 1978-2001; 4 folders (Box CH28)
    - Hyatt Hotels--T-Plan, 1978 (Box CH28)
    - Illinois Dept. of Commerce, 1991 (Box CH28)
    - Illinois Lottery, 1991-2002; 2 folders (Box CH29)
    - Illinois Lottery--Ad agency review, 1999 (Box CH29)
    - Illinois Lottery--JWT booklet, undated (Box CH29)
    - Illinois Lottery--Overview, 2002 (Box CH29)
    - Illinois Lottery--Presentations, 1999-2002; 3 folders (Box CH29)
    - Institute for Health Maintenance, 1982 (Box CH29)
    - Investors Business Daily--Correspondence, 1999 (Box CH29)
    - IOC (International Olympic Committee), 1999 (Box CH29)
    - IOC--Booklet and presentation "The power behind believing", undated (Box CH29)
    - IOC--Project Jenner, 1999; 2 folders (Box CH30)
    - IOC--"Root for mankind" creative, undated (Box CH69)
    - ITBeat--Strategic business plan, 2000 (Box CH30)
    - Joffrey Ballet, 2001 (Box CH30)
    - John Deere, 1999 (Box CH30)
    - Jones-Lundin Associates, 1992 (Box CH30)
    - Joseph Schlitz, 1978 (Box CH30)
    - Joseph Schlitz--Presentation, 1978; 2 folders (Box CH30)
    - Joseph Schlitz--Script for final presentation, 1978 (Box CH30)
    - Kinko's--Advertising historical, undated (Box CH31)
    - Kinko's--Articles, 2001 (Box CH31)
    - Kinko's--Customer study, 2001 (Box CH31)
    - Kino's--Digital website analysis, 2001 (Box CH31)
    - Kinko's--JWT booklet, 2001 (Box CH31)
    - Kinko's--Media plan flowchart, 2001 (Box CH69)
    - Kinko's--Overview, 2001 (Box CH31)
    - Kinko's--Photos, 2001 (Box CH31)
    - Kinko's--Postcards, 2001 (Box CH31)
    - Kinko's--Presentation, 2001 (Box CH31)
    - Konami, 1993 (Box CH31)
    - Konami--Presentation, 1995 (Box CH31)
    - Kraft--Creative, undated (Box CH69)
    - Kraft--Kraft cards, undated (Box CH31)
    - Kraft--Pourables, 1996-1997 (Box CH31)
    - Kraft--Pourables, 1996-1997 (Box CH32)
    - Kraft--Presentation, 1997; 2 folders (Box CH32)
    - Kraft--Mayo: Project Yo, 1996 (Box CH32)
    - Kraftmaid--Cabinetry, 2006; 3 folders (Box CH32)
    - La Quinta, 1994; 3 folders (Box CH32)
    - Learjet, 1994 (Box CH33)
    - Learjet--Final presentation, 1994 (Box CH33)
    - Learjet--Meeting agenda, 1994 (Box CH33)
    - Learjet--Presentation, undated (Box CH69)
    - Learjet--Print ads, 1994 (Box CH33)
    - Lennox, 1992-1994; 2 folders (Box CH33)
    - Lone Star Steakhouse, 1998 (Box CH33)
    - Lone Star Steakhouse, undated (Box CH68)
    - Lowe's (Kitty litter), 1981 (Box CH33)
    - Lucky Stores--Correspondence, 1995 (Box CH33)
    - Lyons Group (Barney Sales Division): See also Barney, 1994-1995; 2 folders (Box CH33)
    - Macy's, 2006 (Box CH34)
    - Marion Laboratories, 1981 (Box CH34)
    - Mattel, 1992-2001; 3 folders (Box CH34)
    - Mattel--1991 toy industry overview, 1992 (Box CH34)
    - Mattel--Annual reports, 1994-1999 (Box CH34)